So, we've built a model,
我们构建了模型
created a Lambda function that lets us interact with that model,
创建了使我们能够与该模型交互的 Lambda 函数
and then created an API or
然后创建了使我们能够
an endpoint that allows us to send data to our lambda function.
向 Lambda 函数发送数据的 API 或端点
The last step is to actually launch our web app.
最后一步是启动网络应用
To do that, we need to know the URL for the endpoint that we've created.
我们需要知道所创建的端点的 URL
If we go back to the API gateway page and select
回到 API Gateway 页面
the API that we created in the last video,
并选择在上个视频中创建的 API
and then on the left-hand side click on "Stages," we can see
然后在左侧点击“Stages”
that there's the single stage we created last time, "prod."
可以看到上次创建的一个阶段“prod”
Selecting this gives us information about our API.
选择“prod”可以查看 API 的信息
In particular at the top here,
在顶部可以看到
it tells us the URL that can be used to invoke the API.
用来调用此 API 的 URL
So, let's copy this.
复制该 URL
If we now go to the "Notebook hub" where we originally opened up the web app notebook,
回到 Notebook Hub 我们一开始打开了 Web App notebook
you can see that there's an index.html file.
可以看到这里有个 index.html 文件
Selecting the check box to the left,
选中左侧的复选框
and then clicking on "Edit" lets us edit this.
然后点击“Edit”编辑该文件
Now, you don't need to know how this webpage works,
你不需要知道这个网页的运行原理
but what you do need to do is make sure you add the name of your deploy endpoint.
但是需要在这里添加部署的端点的名称
This is an old one here, so,
这是以前的名称
I can get rid of it and replace it with the new end point that we just created.
删掉并替换成刚刚创建的端点
Now that we've done that, we can save this file,
然后保存文件
close this page, and now if we open up this webpage,
关闭此页面 现在打开此网页的话
we'll be able to use our web app.
我们将能使用网络应用
For some reason, just clicking on this doesn't seem to work correctly.
因为某种原因 点击它并不能正常运行
However, if I select the check box to the left and
但是 如果选中左侧的复选框
click on "Download," and then run it from my local computer,
点击“Download” 然后在本地计算机上运行
it does seem to work. I'll just zoom in.
的确可以运行放大界面
Now, we can submit some reviews to see
我们可以提交几条影评
whether or not our model thinks they're positive or negative.
看看模型认为是正面的还是负面的
We'll start with a very positive review.
先输入一条很正面的影评
Let's see what our model thinks of this review.
看看模型是怎么认为的
It seems our model was right.
看来模型的预测正确
Okay. How about a negative one?
Ok再输入一条负面的？
We can submit it to our model.
提交给模型
So, our web app is now working.
网络应用现在能正常运行了
Since we don't really have any further use of our web app,
因为不需要再使用该网络应用了
we need to make sure to shut everything down.
所以需要关闭一切
In particular, we need to make sure to shut down our deployed endpoint.
尤其是要关闭部署的端点
Remember, the cost of an endpoint is based on how long it's running for.
端点按运行时长计费
So, if you don't have a use for it, you need to shut it down.
如果不使用 就要关掉
If we head back to the notebook and scroll all the way down to the bottom,
回到 notebook 中并一直向下滚动到底部
we can delete our endpoint by executing this code cell right here.
我们可以执行该代码单元格 删除端点
Of course, you can also use the console as I showed you in a previous video.
当然 也可以使用在之前的视频中演示的控制台方法
In addition to shutting down the endpoint,
除了关闭端点之外
you may wish to delete the lambda function that you
可能还需要删除创建的
created and delete the API that you created.
Lambda 函数以及 API
To do that, heading back to the Amazon console.
切换到 Amazon 控制台
First, to delete the lambda function,
首先删除 Lambda 函数
select "Lambda" under the compute heading
在“Compute”下选择“Lambda”
and you will see the lambda function that you created.
可以看到我们创建的 Lambda 函数
Selecting this, clicking on "Actions" and going down to delete,
选中它 点击“Actions” 然后选择“Delete”
will allow you to delete this lambda function.
将删除此 Lambda 函数
To delete the API that you created,
下面删除创建的 API
go back to the Amazon console,
回到 Amazon 控制台
scroll down to networking and content delivery,
向下滚动到“Networking &amp; Content Delivery”
and select "API Gateway."
选择“API Gateway”
Again, here you will see the API that you created.
在这里可以看到你创建的 API
Select it, click on the "Actions" drop-down and select "Delete API."
选择它 点击“Actions”下拉菜单 然后选择“Delete API”
You'll need to type in the name of your API to confirm that you do want to delete it.
你需要输入 API 的名称 确认你的确想删除它
That's how you can clean up all of the different resources that
这就是清理启动简单网络应用时
you used in order to launch your simple web app.
所使用的所有不同资源的方式